<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="inputstream.adaptive" version="666.21.5.18-p3i.1" name="InputStream Adaptive" provider-name="peak3d, Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" minversion="2.0.0" version="2.0.2"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" minversion="1.0.4" version="1.0.5"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" minversion="5.15.0" version="5.15.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" minversion="1.1.7" version="1.1.9"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.tools" minversion="1.0.0" version="1.0.4"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.inputstream" minversion="3.3.0" version="3.3.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.videocodec" minversion="2.1.0" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.inputstream" name="adaptive" extension="" tags="true" listitemprops="drm_legacy|license_type|license_key|license_url|license_url_append|license_data|license_flags|manifest_type|server_certificate|manifest_update_parameter|manifest_upd_params|manifest_params|manifest_headers|stream_params|stream_headers|original_audio_language|play_timeshift_buffer|pre_init_data|stream_selection_type|chooser_bandwidth_max|chooser_resolution_max|chooser_resolution_secure_max|live_delay|internal_cookies|config|manifest_config" library_linux="inputstream.adaptive.so.21.5.18"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Client InputStream per a transmissions adaptatives</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Klient adaptivních toků protokolu InputStream</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">InputStream-klient til adaptive streams</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">InputStream-Client für adaptive Streams</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">InputStream client for adaptive streams</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Cliente InputStream para transmisiones adaptativas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Cliente InputStream para transmisiones adaptativas</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">InputStream klient kohanduvate voogude jaoks</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">InputStream-asiakas mukautuville mediavirroille</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Client InputStream pour les flux adaptatifs</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">לקוח InputStream לתזרימים מסתגלים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">InputStream klijent za prilagodljiva strujanja</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">InputStream kliens az adaptív streamekhez</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">InputStream-biðlari fyrir aðlaganleg streymi</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Client InputStream per flussi adattivi</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">적응형 스트림을 위한 InputStream 클라이언트</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">InputStream klients adaptīvām straumēm</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">InputStream client voor adaptive streams</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Klient InputStream dla strumieni adaptacyjnych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Cliente InputStream para transmissões adaptáveis</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Клиент InputStream для адаптивных потоков</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">用于自适应流的 InputStream 客户端</summary>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Client InputStream per a transmissions adaptatives</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Klient adaptivních toků protokolu InputStream</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">InputStream-klient til adaptive streams</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">InputStream-Client für adaptive Streams. Unterstützt werden Streamingprotokolle wie MPEG-DASH, HLS und Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR] Das Addon unterstützt ebenfalls DRM-geschützte Streams, wie Google Widevine, Microsoft Playready und andere.[CR][CR]Für Dokumentation https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive besuchen</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">InputStream client for adaptive streams. Common streaming protocols such as MPEG-DASH, HLS and Microsoft Smooth Streaming are supported.[CR][CR]The add-on also has support for DRM protected streams, such as Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady and others.[CR][CR]For documentation visit: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Cliente InputStream para transmisiones de datos adaptativos. Se admiten protocolos de transmisión comunes como MPEG-DASH, HLS y Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]El complemento también es compatible con transmisiones protegidas por DRM, como Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady y otros.[CR][CR]Para consultar la documentación, visite: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Cliente InputStream para transmisiones adaptativas</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">InputStream klient adaptiivsete voogude jaoks. Toetatakse levinud voogedastusprotokolle, nagu MPEG-DASH, HLS ja Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]Lisamoodul toetab ka DRM-iga kaitstud vooge, nagu Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady ja teised.[CR][CR][CR] ]Dokumentatsiooni saamiseks külasta aadressi https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">InputStream-asiakas mukautuville mediavirroille, joka tukee yleisiä suoratoistoprotokollia, kuten MPEG-DASH, HLS ja Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]Tukee myös mm. Google Widevine ja Microsoft PlayReady -tekniikoilla DRM-suojattua suoratoistoa.[CR][CR]Ohjeita löydät osoitteesta https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Client InputStream pour les flux adaptatifs. Les protocoles de streaming courants tels que MPEG-DASH, HLS et Microsoft Smooth Streaming sont pris en charge.[CR][CR]Le module complémentaire prend également en charge les flux protégés par DRM, tels que Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady et autres.[CR][CR] Pour la documentation, visitez : https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">לקוח InputStream לתזרימים מסתגלים</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">InputStream klijent za prilagodljiva strujanja</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">InputStream kliens az adaptív streamekhez</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Client InputStream per flussi adattivi. Sono supportati protocolli di streaming comuni come MPEG-DASH, HLS e Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]L'add-on supporta anche flussi protetti da DRM, come Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady e altri.[CR][CR] ]Per la documentazione visita: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">적응형 스트림을 위한 InputStream 클라이언트입니다. MPEG-DASH, HLS 및 Microsoft Smooth Streaming과 같은 일반적인 스트리밍 프로토콜이 지원됩니다.[CR][CR]추가 기능은 Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady 등과 같은 DRM 보호 스트림도 지원합니다.[CR][CR ]문서를 보려면 https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive를 방문하세요</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">InputStream klients adaptīvām straumēm</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Klient InputStream dla strumieni adaptacyjnych. Obsługiwane są popularne protokoły przesyłania strumieniowego, takie jak MPEG-DASH, HLS i Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]Dodatek obsługuje również strumienie chronione DRM, takie jak Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady i inne.[CR][CR] ]Dokumentacja znajduje się na stronie: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Cliente InputStream para transmissões adaptáveis. Há suporte para protocolos de streaming comuns, como MPEG-DASH, HLS e Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]O addon também oferece suporte a transmissões protegidas por DRM, como Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady e outros.[CR][CR]Para obter a documentação, visite: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Клиент InputStream для адаптивных потоков. Поддерживаются такие распространенные потоковые протоколы, как MPEG-DASH, HLS и Microsoft Smooth Streaming.[CR][CR]Дополнение также поддерживает потоки, защищенные DRM, такие как Google Widevine, Microsoft PlayReady и другие.[CR][CR]Для получения документации посетите: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.adaptive</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">用于自适应流的 InputStream 客户端</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="inputstream.ffmpegdirect" version="666.22.2.5-p3i.1" name="Inputstream FFmpeg Direct" provider-name="Ross Nicholson">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" minversion="2.0.0" version="2.0.2"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" minversion="1.0.4" version="1.0.5"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" minversion="1.1.7" version="1.1.9"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.network" minversion="1.0.0" version="1.0.4"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.tools" minversion="1.0.0" version="1.0.4"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.inputstream" minversion="3.3.0" version="3.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.inputstream" name="ffmpegdirect" extension="" tags="true" listitemprops="program_number|stream_mode|open_mode|manifest_type|default_url|is_realtime_stream|playback_as_live|programme_start_time|programme_end_time|catchup_url_format_string|catchup_url_near_live_format_string|catchup_buffer_start_time|catchup_buffer_end_time|catchup_buffer_offset|catchup_terminates|catchup_granularity|timezone_shift|default_programme_duration|programme_catchup_id" library_linux="inputstream.ffmpegdirect.so.22.2.5"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/runner.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
    <summary lang="bs_BA">InputStream klijent za FFmpeg tokove (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Client InputStream per a fluxos FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Klient toků FFmpeg (libavformat) protokolu InputStream</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">InputStream-klient til FFmpeg-streams (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">InputStream-Client für FFmpeg-Streams (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">InputStream Client for FFmpeg streams (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Cliente de InputStream para transmisiones FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Cliente InputStream para flujos FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">InputStream klient FFmpeg voogudele (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">InputStream-asiakas FFmpeg-mediavirroille (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Client InputStream pour les flux FFmpeg (format libav)</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">InputStream klijent za FFmpeg strujanja (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">InputStream Client per flussi FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">FFmpeg 스트림용 InputStream 클라이언트(libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Klient InputStream dla strumieni FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Cliente InputStream para transmissões FFmpeg (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">InputStream клиент для FFmpeg потоков (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">InputStream-klient för FFmpeg-strömmar (libavformat)</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">FFmpeg 流的 InputStream 客户端（libavformat）</summary>
    <description lang="bs_BA">InputStream klijent za tokove koji se mogu otvoriti pomoću FFmpeg-ovog libavformata ili Kodi-jevog cURL-a. Podržani su uobičajeni formati tokova kao što su običan TS, HLS i DASH (bez DRM-a), kao i mnogi drugi.[CR][CR]Dodatak također ima podršku za usluge arhiviranja/nadoknađivanja gdje postoje prozori za reprodukciju (obično u danima) i može se vremenski pomaknuti kroz taj raspon.[CR][CR]Za dokumentaciju posjetite: https://github.com/xbmc/inputtok.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Client InputStream per a fluxos que es poden obrir mitjançant el libavformat de FFmpeg o el cURL de Kodi. S’admeten formats de flux comuns, com ara TS simple, HLS i DASH (sense DRM), així com molts altres.[CR][CR]El complement també és compatible amb els serveis Archive/Catchup , on hi ha una finestra de reproducció (normalment en dies) i pot canviar de temps en aquest interval.[CR][CR]Per a la documentació, visiteu: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Klient protokolu InputStream pro toky, které mohou být otevřeny pomocí FFmpeg libavformat nebo Kodi cURL.Běžné formáty toků jako prosté TS, HLS, DASH (bez DRM) a mnoho dalších jsou podporovány.[CR][CR]Doplněk má též podporu pro služby Archive/Catchup, které mají dobu pro opětovné přehrání (obvykle ve dnech) a mohou mít v tomto období časový posun.[CR][CR]Pro dokumentaci navštivte: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">InputStream-klient til streams, der kan åbnes af enten FFmpeg's libavformat eller Kodi's cURL. Almindelige streamformater som f.eks. almindelig TS, HLS og DASH (uden DRM) understøttes såvel som mange andre.[CR][CR]Add-on'et har også understøttelse af arkiv-/indhentningstjenester, hvor der er et afspilningsvindue (normalt i dage) og kan tidsforskyde på tværs af dette spænd.[CR][CR]For dokumentation besøg: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">InputStream-Client für Streams, die entweder mit dem libav-Format von FFmpeg oder mit cURL von Kodi geöffnet werden können. Gängige Stream-Formate wie TS, HLS und DASH (ohne DRM) werden ebenso unterstützt wie viele andere.[CR][CR]Das Addon unterstützt auch Archiv-/Aufholdienste, bei denen Wiedergabefenster vorhanden sind (normalerweise in Tagen), und kann über diesen Zeitraum hinweg eine Zeitverschiebung bewirken.[CR][CR]Dokumentation unter: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">InputStream Client for streams that can be opened by either FFmpeg's libavformat or Kodi's cURL. Common stream formats such as plain TS, HLS and DASH (without DRM) are supported as well as many others.[CR][CR]The addon also has support for Archive/Catchup services where there is a replay windows (usually in days) and can timeshift across that span.[CR][CR]For documenation visit: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Cliente InputStream para transmisiones que se pueden abrir mediante libavformat de FFmpeg o cURL de Kodi. Se admiten formatos de transmisión comunes, como TS simple, HLS y DASH (sin DRM), así como muchos otros.[CR][CR]El complemento también es compatible con los servicios Archive/Catchup donde hay ventanas de repetición (generalmente en días) y puede realizar timeshift durante ese lapso.[CR][CR]Para documentación visita: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Cliente InputStream para flujos de datos que pueden abrirse con libavformat de FFmpeg o cURL integrado en Kodi. Formatos de flujo comunes tales como TS simple, HLS y DASH (sin DRM) también están soportados, al igual que muchos otros.[CR][CR]El complemento también soporta servicios Archive/Catchup donde hay un espacio de repetición (usualmente en días) y se puede mover a través del tiempo de dicho espacio.[CR][CR]Para documentación visita: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">InputStream klient voogudele, mida avavad kas FFmpeg libavformat või Kodi cURL. Toetatakse tavalisi vorminguid, nagu TS, HLS ja DASH (ilma DRM-ita), aga ka paljusid teisi.[CR][CR]Lisamoodul toetab ka järelvaatamise teenuseid, kus ajanihe on võimalik teatud ajavahemikus (tavaliselt päevades).[CR][CR]Dokumentatsiooni saamiseks külasta: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">InputStream-asiakas mediavirroille, jotka voidaan avata joko FFmpegin libavformat- tai Kodi cURL-kirjastolla. Monien muiden ohella tuetaan yleisiä mediavirtamuotoja, kuten puhdas TS, HLS ja DASH (ilman DRM-suojausta).[CR][CR]Lisäosa tukee myös Archive-/Catchup-palveluita, joissa toisto ja ajansiirto on mahdollista tiettyjen ajanjaksojen sisällä (yleensä päiviä).[CR][CR]Ohjeita löytyy täältä: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">InputStream Client pour les flux pouvant être ouverts soit par le libavformat de FFmpeg, soit par le cURL de Kodi. Les formats de flux courants tels que TS, HLS et DASH (sans DRM) sont pris en charge ainsi que bien d'autres. et peut être décalé dans le temps dans la période.[CR][CR]Pour la documentation, visitez : https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">InputStream klijent za strujanja koja se mogu otvoriti ili FFmpeg libavformatom ili Kodijevim cURL-om. Uobičajeni formati strujanja poput običnog TS, HLS i DASH (bez DRM zaštite sadržaja) formata su podržani kao i mnogi drugi.[CR][CR]Dodatak ima još podršku za Arhive/Hvatanje usluga gdje postoji prozor ponovne raprodukcije (uobičajeno u danima) i može se vremenski premotavati u zadanom vremenskom razdoblju.[CR][CR]Za dokumentaciju posjetite: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Client InputStream per flussi che possono essere aperti da libavformat di FFmpeg o cURL di Kodi. Sono supportati formati di flussi comuni come TS, HLS e DASH (senza DRM) e molti altri.[CR][CR]L'add-on ha anche il supporto per i servizi Archivio/Recupero in cui è presente una finestra di riproduzione (di solito in giorni) e può passare attraverso tale intervallo.[CR][CR]Per la documentazione visita: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">FFmpeg의 libavformat 또는 Kodi의 cURL로 열 수 있는 스트림용 InputStream 클라이언트. 일반 TS, HLS 및 DASH(DRM 제외)와 같은 일반적인 스트림 형식은 물론 다른 많은 형식도 지원됩니다.[CR][CR]이 애드온은 재생 창(보통 며칠)이 있는 아카이브/따라잡기 서비스도 지원합니다. 해당 범위에서 타임시프트할 수 있습니다.[CR][CR]문서를 보려면 https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md를 방문하세요</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Klient InputStream dla strumieni, które można otworzyć za pomocą libavformat FFmpeg lub cURL Kodi. Obsługiwane są popularne formaty strumieniowe, takie jak zwykły TS, HLS i DASH (bez DRM), a także wiele innych.[CR][CR]Dodatek obsługuje również usługę archiwizacji, która zapewnia okno powtórek (zazwyczaj w dniach) i może wykonywać przesunięcie czasowe przez ten zakres.[CR][CR]W celu uzyskania dokumentacji odwiedź: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Cliente InputStream para transmissões que podem ser abertas pelo libavformat do FFmpeg ou pelo cURL do Kodi. Os formatos de transmissão comuns, como TS simples, HLS e DASH (sem DRM), são suportados, bem como muitos outros.[CR][CR]O addon também tem suporte para serviços de Arquivo/Catchup em que há uma janela de reprodução (geralmente em dias) e pode mudar o tempo ao longo desse intervalo.[CR][CR]Para obter documentação, visite: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Клиент InputStream для потоков, которые можно открыть с помощью libavformat от FFmpeg или с помощью Kodi cURL. Поддерживаются основные форматы потоков такие, как простой TS, HLS, DASH (без DRM) и многие другие.[CR][CR]Дополнение также имеет поддержку служб Архива/Перемотки, где есть окна воспроизведения (обычно в днях), которые могут сдвигаться по времени в течение этого промежутка.[CR][CR]Для документации посетите: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">InputStream Klient för strömmar som kan öppnas av antingen FFmpegs libavformat eller Kodis cURL. Vanliga strömformat som vanlig TS, HLS och DASH (utan DRM) stöds liksom många andra.[CR][CR]Tillägget har också stöd för arkiv / catchup-tjänster där det finns ett uppspelningsfönster (vanligtvis i dagar) och kan tidsförskjutas över det spannet.[CR][CR]För dokumentation besök: https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">InputStream 客户端，用于可通过 FFmpeg 的 libavformat 或 Kodi 的 cURL 打开的流。支持普通 TS、HLS 和 DASH（无DRM）等常见流格式以及其他许多格式。[CR][CR]该插件还支持有重播窗口（通常以天为单位）的归档/捕获服务，并可以在该时间跨度内进行时光平移。[CR][CR]相关文档请访问：https://github.com/xbmc/inputstream.ffmpegdirect/blob/Matrix/README.md</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper"
version="6.15.6-p3i.1"
name="TMDb Helper"
provider-name="jurialmunkey">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
  <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
  <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
  <import addon="script.module.addon.signals" version="0.0.6" />
  <import addon="script.module.jurialmunkey" version="0.2.35" />
  <import addon="script.module.infotagger" version="0.0.5" />
  <import addon="script.module.qrcode" version="6.1.0" />
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/plugin.py">
  <provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="resources/script.py" />
<extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/service.py" />
<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/modules"/>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
  <summary lang="de_DE">TMDb Helfer</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">TMDb Helper</summary>
  <summary lang="es_ES">Asistente TMDb</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">TMDb 助手</summary>
  <description lang="de_DE">TMDb Helper liefert Details über Filme, Fernsehsendungen und Schauspieler aus TMDb. Benutzer können auf eine Vielzahl von Listen aus TMDb TVDb MDbList und Trakt zugreifen.</description>
  <description lang="en_GB">TMDb Helper provides details about movies, tvshows and actors from TMDb. Users can access a variety of lists from TMDb TVDb MDbList and Trakt.</description>
  <description lang="es_ES">TMDb Helper proporciona detalles sobre películas, series y actores de TMDb. Los usuarios pueden acceder a una variedad de listas de TMDb, TVDb, MDbList y Trakt.</description>
  <description lang="pl_PL">TMDb Helper dostarcza szczegółowych informacji o filmach, serialach i aktorach z serwisu TMDb. Użytkownicy mają dostęp do szeregu list z serwisów TMDb, TVDb, MDbList i Trakt.</description>
  <description lang="sv_SE">TMDb Helper tillhandahåller information om filmer, tv-serier och skådespelare från TMDb. Användare kan få tillgång till en mängd olika listor från TMDb, TVDb, MDbList och Trakt.</description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">TMDb 助手从 TMDb（影视数据库） 获取电影、电视剧及演员的详细信息。用户可访问来自 TMDb、TVDb、MDbList 和 Trakt 的各类影视列表。</description>
  <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Daten bereitgestellt von TMDb TVDb MDbList OMDb FanartTV und Trakt. Einige der Informationen werden von TheTVDB.com bereitgestellt. Bitte erwäge sie zu unterstützen. https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Data provided by TMDb TVDb MDbList OMDb FanartTV and Trakt. Some of the information is provided by TheTVDB.com. Please consider supporting them. https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Datos proporcionados por TMDb, TVDb, MDbList, OMDb, FanartTV y Trakt. Parte de la información es suministrada por TheTVDB.com. Por favor, considera apoyarles. https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Dane dostarczane przez TMDb TVDb MDbList OMDb FanartTV i Trakt. Niektóre informacje pochodzą z serwisu TheTVDB.com. Prosimy o rozważenie wsparcia tych serwisów. https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Data tillhandahållen av TMDb TVDb MDbList OMDb FanartTV och Trakt. En del av informationen tillhandahålls av TheTVDB.com. Stöd dem gärna. https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">数据由 TMDb、TVDb、MDbList、OMDb、FanartTV 和 Trakt 提供。部分信息由 TheTVDB.com 提供，建议您支持他们。订阅链接：https://thetvdb.com/subscribe</disclaimer>
  <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
  <website>https://github.com/jurialmunkey/plugin.video.themoviedb.helper</website>
  <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=345847</forum>
  <assets>
    <icon>icon.png</icon>
    <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    <clearlogo>clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
    <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
    <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
  </assets>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.p3i" name="p3i" version="0.1.2" provider-name="pannal">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="p3i Kodi Repo">
        <dir minversion="20.90.0">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pannal/p3i_repo/master/omega/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pannal/p3i_repo/master/omega/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pannal/p3i_repo/master/omega/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>p3i</summary>
        <description>Binary and Python addons built for the p3i CoreELEC build (aml-4.9-21.3 lineage).</description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.embuary.helper" name="Embuary Helper" version="2.0.9-p3i.1" provider-name="sualfred">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>v2.0.9-p3i.1: Skip the background fanart grabber and PIL blur while anything is playing (they ran synchronously on the service thread every ~200s and caused microstutters on constrained boxes). Gated on isPlaying so pauses/seeks cannot let it slip through and hitch playback on resume. Based on upstream 2.0.9. Upstream PR: sualfred/script.embuary.helper#73</news>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=345318</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/sualfred/script.embuary.helper</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Embuary Helper Script</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Helper script to provide features and functions to the Embuary skin. A full documentation can be found on GitHub: https://github.com/sualfred/script.embuary.helper/wiki</description>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.jurialmunkey" name="jurialmunkey common" provider-name="jurialmunkey" version="0.2.35">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.infotagger" version="0.0.5" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/modules" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en_GB">Common code required by TMDbHelper and other related jurialmunkey add-ons</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">TMDb 助手及其他相关 jurialmunkey 插件所需的通用代码</description>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <website>https://github.com/jurialmunkey/script.module.jurialmunkey</website>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.override" name="p3i Per-Folder Setting Override" version="0.1.8" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Per-folder Kodi setting overrides via override.ini.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Opt-in service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. Reads "override.ini" from the playing file's folder and one parent folder, applies any Kodi setting overrides listed there at AV-start, and restores the previous values on stop. INI format: bare "kodi.setting.id = value" lines, or [global] and [filename or glob] sections that cover flat libraries and TV season folders without scattering files. Cascade is broadest-first, narrower wins. Ships with a verified-settings catalog covering Dolby Vision dynamic knobs (CMv4.0 append, L5 active-area override and enable surfaces), LAV seamless-branching mode, and the subtitle pipeline (PGS HDR-to-SDR shader tonemap params, style, render-time settings) — entries outside the catalog still write, but log a warning that mid-playback effect isn't guaranteed. If service.p3i.sb is installed, override.ini entries for the LAV seamless-branching key are skipped — that addon owns the key. Unlike the SB helper, this addon does not defer to PlexMod4Kodi: PM4K's Plex streams use http(s) URLs which are skipped by the remote-scheme filter, and for local files played through PM4K the user's override.ini still applies as written.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.6" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.16" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.15.2" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.15.1" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.15" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.13.1" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.13" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.12" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.11" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.10" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.p3i.estuary" version="8.8.9" name="p3i.Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Estuary هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Estuary - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Estuary on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Estuary adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Estuary là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.embuary.helper" name="Embuary Helper" version="2.0.8-p3i.1" provider-name="sualfred">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Embuary Helper Script</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Helper script to provide features and functions to the Embuary skin. A full documentation can be found on GitHub: https://github.com/sualfred/script.embuary.helper/wiki</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>v2.0.8-p3i.1: Skip the background fanart grabber and PIL blur while anything is playing (they ran synchronously on the service thread every ~200s and caused microstutters on constrained boxes). Gated on isPlaying so pauses/seeks cannot let it slip through and hitch playback on resume.</news>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=345318</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/sualfred/script.embuary.helper</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.override" name="p3i Per-Folder Setting Override" version="0.1.7" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Per-folder Kodi setting overrides via override.ini.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Opt-in service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. Reads "override.ini" from the playing file's folder and one parent folder, applies any Kodi setting overrides listed there at AV-start, and restores the previous values on stop. INI format: bare "kodi.setting.id = value" lines, or [global] and [filename or glob] sections that cover flat libraries and TV season folders without scattering files. Cascade is broadest-first, narrower wins. Ships with a verified-settings catalog covering Dolby Vision dynamic knobs (CMv4.0 append, L5 active-area override and enable surfaces), LAV seamless-branching mode, and the subtitle pipeline (PGS HDR-to-SDR shader tonemap params, style, render-time settings) — entries outside the catalog still write, but log a warning that mid-playback effect isn't guaranteed. If service.p3i.sb is installed, override.ini entries for the LAV seamless-branching key are skipped — that addon owns the key. Unlike the SB helper, this addon does not defer to PlexMod4Kodi: PM4K's Plex streams use http(s) URLs which are skipped by the remote-scheme filter, and for local files played through PM4K the user's override.ini still applies as written.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.override" name="p3i Per-Folder Setting Override" version="0.1.6" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Per-folder Kodi setting overrides via override.ini.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Opt-in service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. Reads "override.ini" from the playing file's folder and one parent folder, applies any Kodi setting overrides listed there at AV-start, and restores the previous values on stop. INI format: bare "kodi.setting.id = value" lines, or [global] and [filename or glob] sections that cover flat libraries and TV season folders without scattering files. Cascade is broadest-first, narrower wins. Ships with a verified-settings catalog covering Dolby Vision dynamic knobs (CMv4.0 append, L5 active-area override and enable surfaces), LAV seamless-branching mode, and the subtitle pipeline (PGS HDR-to-SDR shader tonemap params, style, render-time settings) — entries outside the catalog still write, but log a warning that mid-playback effect isn't guaranteed. If service.p3i.sb is installed, override.ini entries for the LAV seamless-branching key are skipped — that addon owns the key. Unlike the SB helper, this addon does not defer to PlexMod4Kodi: PM4K's Plex streams use http(s) URLs which are skipped by the remote-scheme filter, and for local files played through PM4K the user's override.ini still applies as written.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.override" name="p3i Per-Folder Setting Override" version="0.1.5" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Per-folder Kodi setting overrides via override.ini.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Opt-in service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. Reads "override.ini" from the playing file's folder and one parent folder, applies any Kodi setting overrides listed there at AV-start, and restores the previous values on stop. INI format: bare "kodi.setting.id = value" lines, or [global] and [filename or glob] sections that cover flat libraries and TV season folders without scattering files. Cascade is broadest-first, narrower wins. Ships with a verified-settings catalog covering Dolby Vision dynamic knobs (CMv4.0 append, L5 active-area override and enable surfaces), LAV seamless-branching mode, and the subtitle pipeline (PGS HDR-to-SDR shader tonemap params, style, render-time settings) — entries outside the catalog still write, but log a warning that mid-playback effect isn't guaranteed. If service.p3i.sb is installed, override.ini entries for the LAV seamless-branching key are skipped — that addon owns the key. Unlike the SB helper, this addon does not defer to PlexMod4Kodi: PM4K's Plex streams use http(s) URLs which are skipped by the remote-scheme filter, and for local files played through PM4K the user's override.ini still applies as written.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.5" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.4" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.3" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.2" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.1" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.p3i.sb" name="p3i Seamless Branching Helper" version="0.1.0" provider-name="pannal">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Auto-enables the CoreELEC LAV seamless-branching workaround for known SB titles.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Service addon for the p3i CoreELEC build. When a movie with a known seamless-branching audio issue (TrueHD or tms EAC3) starts playing, this addon toggles the CoreELEC LAV filter mode to avoid audio dropouts, and restores the previous mode on stop. Matches both IMDb and TMDB IDs against a bundled, curated list. Defers automatically when PlexMod4Kodi (script.plexmod) is running, since PM4K handles the same workaround for Plex-sourced playback.</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/pannal/p3i_repo</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
